#### Contact

oakley.trotter@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/oakley-trotter-rn-bsn-ccrn-116950a3 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

ICU

Nursing

**BLS** 

Certifications
CCRN

# Oakley Trotter RN, BSN, CCRN

Travel Nurse at LRS Healthcare

New Orleans, Louisiana

### Summary

Experienced Critical Care Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), Intensive Care, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and Patient Safety. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Northwestern State University.

## Experience

LRS Healthcare
Travel Nurse
October 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)
ICU RN

FlexCare Medical Staffing
Travel Nurse
May 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)
ICU RN

10 years 2 months
ICU Director
October 2015 - June 2018 (2 years 9 months)

New Orleans

**Touro Infirmary** 

SICU Clinical Supervisor May 2008 - February 2016 (7 years 10 months)

Tulane Medical Center
Critical Care RN
May 2010 - May 2018 (8 years 1 month)
New Orleans, Louisiana

## Education

Northwestern State University
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse